{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866265786","data":{"timestamp":" 946866265785"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-3-8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866270722","data":{"timestamp":" 946866270722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-5-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866275942","data":{"timestamp":" 946866275942"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_5-0-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866280729","data":{"timestamp":" 946866280729"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_5-0-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866285475","data":{"timestamp":" 946866285475"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_5-0-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866291519","data":{"timestamp":" 946866291519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_3-8-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866296599","data":{"timestamp":" 946866296599"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_3-8-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866304023","data":{"timestamp":" 946866304023"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-0-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866310256","data":{"timestamp":" 946866310256"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-3-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866317142","data":{"timestamp":" 946866317142"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-3-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866330085","data":{"timestamp":" 946866330084"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_4-3-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866335925","data":{"timestamp":" 946866335925"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866341884","data":{"timestamp":" 946866341884"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866348268","data":{"timestamp":" 946866348268"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866359123","data":{"timestamp":" 946866359123"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866365675","data":{"timestamp":" 946866365673"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" faca3a70-0f5d-4278-b9f6-9c1cd04b8799"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866383697","data":{"timestamp":" 946866383697"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 49e3412f-ba29-4c9f-8fa4-f3e4c948a4c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-3-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866421032","data":{"timestamp":" 946866421032"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 49e3412f-ba29-4c9f-8fa4-f3e4c948a4c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-3-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866428567","data":{"timestamp":" 946866428566"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 49e3412f-ba29-4c9f-8fa4-f3e4c948a4c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-3-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866441288","data":{"timestamp":" 946866441288"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866449196","data":{"timestamp":" 946866449195"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TWIGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866450808","data":{"timestamp":" 946866450807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866454250","data":{"timestamp":" 946866454249"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TEMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866455863","data":{"timestamp":" 946866455862"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866458326","data":{"timestamp":" 946866458326"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866459950","data":{"timestamp":" 946866459949"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866462997","data":{"timestamp":" 946866462997"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TANO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866464546","data":{"timestamp":" 946866464546"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866464784","data":{"timestamp":" 946866464784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866464888","data":{"timestamp":" 946866464888"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_052412"," gameId":" 3e6f1b23-9ef4-467f-80e5-2e5bc31c0f71"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" TIKITI MAJI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}